emagicone.com 2019-05-18

# eMagicOne | Privacy Statement - eMagicOne

## **Introduction**

eMagicOne values the privacy and security of the information that you share with us. This Privacy Statement applies to information collected by eMagicOne through the following websites and applications: 

**Company/product websites:**

  * emagicone.com
  * store.emagicone.com
  * escraper.emagicone.com
  * license.emagicone.com
  * www.mag-manager.com
  * www.prestashopmanager.com
  * woocommerce-manager.com
  * www.opencartmanager.com
  * virtuemart-manager.com
  * www.zencart-manager.com

**Software:**

  * Store Manager for Magento and its addons, modules, connectors
  * Store Manager for PrestaShop and its addons, modules, connectors
  * Store Manager for WooCommerce and its addons, modules, connectors
  * Store Manager for OpenCart and its addons, modules, connectors
  * Store Manager for VirtueMart and its addons, modules, connectors
  * Store Manager for Zen Cart and its addons, modules, connectors
  * Mobile Assistant applications and its connectors

**Help center:**

  * support.emagicone.com

This Privacy Statement also applies to other information eMagicOne receives in the United States from Europe. This Statement describes how eMagicOne collects, uses, shares, protects, or otherwise processes your personal information. By using this website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Statement. 

## **Collection and Use of Information**

eMagicOne collects personal information to set up and manage accounts for our ecommerce products and services and to handle orders of goods and services developed by eMagicOne. 

You may need to provide eMagicOne with personal information such as: 

  * names; phone numbers; mailing, billing, shipping, and email addresses; Internet Protocol address;

### **eMagicOne uses such information for:**

  * product registration; enabling sales and other transactions; processing payments and settlement; sending payouts; handling orders; providing receipts and/or invoices;
  * providing customer service; providing dispute resolution, chargebacks, refunds, or related issues;
  * marketing and surveys; sending service update notices;
  * detecting and preventing fraud; detecting and preventing violations of our legal agreements;
  * measuring, improving, and customizing our services; and
  * fulfilling other technical, logistical, financial, tax, legal, compliance, administrative, or back office functions.

eMagicOne may also collect background information from third parties to verify your identity; deter, detect, and prevent fraud and illegal activity; make business decisions; and as a part of our legal obligations. eMagicOne retains such information for as long as reasonably required for business purposes or as reasonably required to comply with our legal obligations. 

### **Software Information**

eMagicOne may also collect information from installation/registration to verify your identity, to create license key (trial), to verify license key, to prevent violations of our license agreements. eMagicOne may also collect background information to verify your identity, product usage and performance. Such information may include your email address; Internet Protocol address; date and time of activity; name of the software and/or section; general usage statistics; software logs and depersonalised statistical data. 

eMagicOne uses information gathered from Software to track the violation of license policy; monitor product performance; improve product design, functionality, and security; and assemble analytics and activity trends. eMagicOne retains such information for as long as reasonably required for business purposes or as reasonably required to comply with our legal obligations

### **Community Information**

eMagicOne collects information from you to post entries to our support website or forums. Such information may include your email address, Internet Protocol address, user name, date and time of signup, and date and time of posts to the forum, feature request, survey, live chat feedback or any other public post. 

eMagicOne uses this information for the secure and efficient functioning of our website, to provide you with access to our community site, to detect and prevent violations of our legal agreements, and as part of any legal obligations related to our community website. 

### **Transaction Information**

eMagicOne collects information on each transaction conducted through our website. Such information may include the amount of the transaction; the goods purchased; the identity of the seller, affiliate, and customer; payment type; currency; location; Internet Protocol address; and websites visited. 

eMagicOne uses such information for refunds, for customer service, for website optimization, or for other administrative or business purposes. eMagicOne may collect and share information related to the transactions you conduct through our website with partners or resellers for the purposes disclosed in this Privacy Statement. eMagicOne retains transaction information for as long as reasonably required for business purposes or as reasonably required to comply with our legal obligations. 

### PayPal

eMagicOne uses PayPal, a payment processor. PayPal uses cookies, web beacons, and other means to help eMagicOne process the payments. You may find PayPal’s Privacy Policy at https://www.paypal.com/be/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full 

### MyCommerce

eMagicOne uses MyCommerce, a payment processor. MyCommerce uses cookies, web beacons, and other means to help eMagicOne process the payments and analyze how users use the site. You may find MyCommerce’s Privacy Policy at https://www.mycommerce.com/corporate-policy/ 

### PayPro Global

eMagicOne uses PayPro Global, a payment processor. PayPro Global uses cookies, web beacons, and other means to help eMagicOne process the payments and analyze how users use the site. You may find PayPro Global’s Privacy Policy at https://payproglobal.com/legal 

To protect your information during the payment, we use payment processors which use modern technologies for secure transactions. Account passwords on all our websites are encrypted. 

### **Customer Service Correspondence**

eMagicOne also collects information involving customer service correspondence. This information may include emails, internet chats, faxes, or telephone calls directed to our customer service center. eMagicOne processes this information to provide customer service, handle complaints or disputes, measure and improve our customer service, detect and prevent fraud, and detect and prevent violations of our legal agreements. eMagicOne retains customer service information for as long as reasonably required for business purposes or as reasonably required to comply with our legal obligations. 

### LiveAgent

eMagicOne uses LiveAgent, CRM software. LiveAgent uses e-mail, Internet Protocol address, cookies, web beacons, and other means to allow eMagicOne provide support. You may find LiveAgent’s Privacy Statement at https://www.ladesk.com/gdpr

### **Cookies, Web Beacons, and Logs**

eMagicOne collects information related to your use of our website using cookies, web beacons, and log information. 

Cookies are small files containing strings of text stored on your computer. eMagicOne uses cookies to authenticate you as a user when you log in, track your session, deliver content specific to your preferences and interests, store the contents of your shopping cart, provide features related to payment and customer service, and provide other functions. 

Web beacons are objects embedded into web pages that allow us to determine whether and for how long users view web pages. We use web beacons for site traffic reporting, unique visitor counts, auditing and reporting, personalization, and other functions. 

Log information may include web requests, Internet Protocol address, operating system, browser type, browser language, date and time of your request, and cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. eMagicOne uses this information to enhance the functionality of the website and to make your access more convenient, secure, and efficient. 

eMagicOne also uses information gathered from logs, cookies, and web beacons to monitor website performance; improve website design, functionality, and security; and assemble web analytics and activity trends. eMagicOne retains such information for as long as reasonably required for business purposes or as reasonably required to comply with our legal obligations. 

You may stop your browser from accepting cookies or web beacons. The Help portion of your browser should explain how to configure your browser’s cookie handling. Your browser may have add-ons that may help you block web beacons. You may have limited functionality if you block cookies or web beacons set by our website. 

### Google AdWords

eMagicOne uses Google AdWords, a web analytics and search engine advertising campaign management service. Google AdWords uses cookies, web beacons, and other means to help eMagicOne analyze how users use the site. You may find Google’s Privacy Statement at http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacypolicy.html 

### Google Analytics

eMagicOne uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service. Google Analytics uses cookies, web beacons, and other means to help eMagicOne analyze how users use the site. You may find Google’s Privacy Policy at http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacypolicy.html 

### Google Suite

eMagicOne uses Google Suite, a web mail and cloud data collection and storage service. Google Suite uses cookies, web beacons, and other means to help eMagicOne process emails, gather information from forms, store aggregated data. 2-step verification is used to ensure data safety. You may find Google’s Privacy Policy at https://policies.google.com/privacy 

### FaceBook

eMagicOne uses FaceBook, a social media and marketing service. FaceBook uses cookies, web beacons, and other means to help eMagicOne analyze how users use the site. You may find FaceBook’s Privacy Policy at https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation 

### **Other**

### LeaseWeb

eMagicOne uses LeaseWeb, a hosting company located in Europe. You may find LeaseWeb’s Privacy Policy at https://www.leaseweb.com/legal 

## **Choice**

We will seek your consent prior to using your personal information in a manner incompatible with the purposes we described in our Privacy Statement at the time of collection. You may choose not to provide any personal information to eMagicOne, in which case we will be unable to provide services to you. 

## **Sharing of Information**

eMagicOne only shares information as described in this Privacy Statement. Your personal information will be shared within the inner structure of the company and only for purposes of improving our products, providing development and/or support service, providing better services and advertising them. Your personally identifiable information will not be used by us for any further purposes, nor sold or shared with third parties. 

eMagicOne shares information with the following categories of third parties. Such third parties are prohibited by law or by contract from processing personal information for purposes other than those disclosed in this Privacy Statement. 

### **Organizations that Provide Services to Us**

eMagicOne discloses personal information to other organizations that perform services on our behalf. We require such organizations to use such information solely for the purposes of providing services to us and to protect the personal information with appropriate safeguards. 

Such organizations include financial institutions; payment processors; money transfer service providers; auditors; background and credit check organizations; fraud prevention service providers and anti-fraud networks; marketing service providers; database managers; customer service providers and representatives; and others who perform technical, logistical, financial, tax, legal, compliance, or administrative functions on our behalf. 

These organizations may perform functions such as processing credit and debit card payments, sending wire transfers, providing background and credit checks, providing fraud checks, providing customer service, analyzing data, supplying marketing assistance, fulfilling orders, sending email, and providing other financial, technical, logistical, tax, legal, compliance, or administrative functions. 

### **Re-Sellers**

eMagicOne discloses personal information to its re-sellers. eMagicOne provides access to customer e-mail, first and last name for license creation to re-sellers who make goods and services available to customers for purchase on those re-seller’s websites. 

### **Partners**

eMagicOne may share personal information to its partners. eMagicOne provides access to customer e-mail, country, date of transaction, product name, order totals, first and last name for administrative purposes like accounting, billing and audits, and other uses. 

### **Other**

eMagicOne may disclose personal information where: 

  * required by law or by an order or requirement of a court, administrative agency, or other government entity, or by court rules concerning the production of records;
  * eMagicOne has reasonable grounds to believe that use or disclosure is necessary to protect the rights, privacy, property, or safety of our users or others;
  * eMagicOne has reasonable grounds to believe that the information relates to the breach of an agreement or violation of the law that has been, is being, or is about to be committed;
  * it is necessary for fraud protection, risk reduction, or the establishment or collection of funds owed to us;
  * it is necessary to enforce or apply our legal agreements, to pursue remedies, or to limit damages to eMagicOne;
  * the information is public;
  * you have provided consent or with your direction; or
  * other reasons allow it or other laws require it.

When we are required or permitted to disclose information, we will not disclose more information than is necessary to fulfill the disclosure purpose. 

eMagicOne may disclose aggregate or statistical information to our business partners, for public relations purposes, or other purposes. 

## **Access**

At your request, we will provide you with reasonable access to your personal information, so that you can review what we have stored and, if you choose, request corrections to it. You may request access by writing to us at the address listed in the Contact Information section at https://support.emagicone.com/submit_ticket identifying yourself accordingly. 

After you request access, we will provide the personal information that you request as soon as practically possible and generally no later than thirty (30) days following the request. If you wish to correct your personal information, please send us a written explanation of the particular information that you believe should be corrected. Where information will not or cannot be accessed or amended, we will tell you the reasons. 

eMagicOne stores, collects, and otherwise processes information mainly in Plymouth, MN, U.S.A; Frankfurt, Germany; and Ternopil, Ukraine. 

If you are residing in the European Union/ the European Economic Area, you have the right to: 

  * access your personal information, rectify it, restrict or object to its processing, or request its deletion,
  * to receive the personal information you provided to eMagicOne or to transmit it to another company. More specifically, based on the European Union laws, you may request and receive copies of the personal information that you have provided to us in a structured, commonly used, and machine-readable format and/or request us to transmit this information to another service provider (where technically feasible),
  * to withdraw any consent provided,
  * to opt out of some collection or uses of your personal information, including the use of cookies and similar technologies, the use of your personal information for marketing purposes, and the use for data analyses,
  * where applicable, to lodge a complaint with your supervisory authority.

We encourage to contact us and we will respond in due time to settle all your questions and requests to the extent permitted by law. 

## **Security**

We work to protect your personal information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the information that you provide online at our website. We offer Secure SHell (SSH) tunneling to provide secure data transfer between your online store connection with eMagicOne’s software installed on your personal computer. No data is transferred to our servers in We will use commercially reasonable efforts to protect your information. We will also continue to assess new technology for protecting information and upgrade our information security systems when appropriate. 

Further, we permit only authorized eMagicOne employees and third parties to access any personal information. If an employee misuses personal information, we may take disciplinary action, up to and including termination of employment. If any third party individual or organization misuses personal information, we will take action, up to and including termination of any agreement between eMagicOne and that individual or organization and inform you accordingly. 

## **Data Integrity**

eMagicOne processes personal information only for the purposes it was originally collected and in accordance with this Privacy Statement. eMagicOne takes commercially reasonable steps to ensure that the personal data is relevant, reliable for its intended use, accurate, complete, and current for the purposes for which it is used. eMagicOne retains information for as long as reasonably required for business purposes or as reasonably required to comply with our legal obligations. 

## **Links to Other Websites**

When you click on a link on this website that takes you to a website operated by another company, you will be subject to that company’s privacy practices. 

## **Controlling Unsolicited Email**

We may send you information about our products and services. You may send us mail to unsubscribe@emagicone.com indicating the e-mail that you do not want to receive mails and email type that you do not want to receive any more (marketing, licensing, support, etc). so we could update your Preferences and you will stop receiving this information accordingly. You may also opt out of eMagicOne marketing list or update your information by notifying us at contact@emagicone.com at any time. 

## **Amendments**

eMagicOne may amend this Privacy Statement on one or more occasions by posting a revised statement on this website or a similar website that replaces this website. eMagicOne will amend this Privacy Statement in a manner consistent with the Safe Harbor Principles. 

## **Enforcement, Dispute Resolution, and Verification**

Please contact us with any questions or concerns related to this Privacy Statement by using the email address contact@emagicone.com 

## **Contact Information**

If you have questions or concerns related to this Privacy Statement, you may contact us by email at contact@emagicone.com or by writing to us at: 

Attn: Privacy Officer  
Email: dpo@emagicone.com  
eMagicOne, LLC  
PO Box 46353,  
Plymouth, MN 55447  
USA 

05/24/2018
